<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cibil Dashboard</title>
    <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cibil Dashboard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:00:32 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Compare Loan Offers</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:00:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/testing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Your Information</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/consumer-awareness/protecting-your-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:28:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/consumer-awareness/protecting-your-information/</guid>
      <description>Below are some Tips on how to protect your Data Online:-
Mobile security tips
Research and download apps from a safe, trusted source.
Read the terms and conditions around app permissions before clicking on &amp;ldquo;I agree&amp;rdquo;.
Review the app ratings before deciding whether the content is appropriate for download.
Ensure your apps are updated regularly and watch out for new updates or permissions that the app may require.
If you are using a banking app or any other app for financial transactions, follow basic tips such as protecting your phone with a password, not changing factory security settings and/or logging out from the app when finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phishing Techniques</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/consumer-awareness/phishing-techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:06:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/consumer-awareness/phishing-techniques/</guid>
      <description>At TransUnion CIBIL, we aim to provide Information for Good. With our consumers&amp;rsquo; data at the centre of our business, we strive to secure your information and ensure it is protected. However, we need your cooperation in this constant fight against fraud. Have you ever realised how easy it is to fall prey to credit fraud and identity theft?
Despite the advances in the digital world, there are innumerable ways in which you can expose your confidential information online and put yourself at risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offers Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/legal-information/offers-terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:55:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/legal-information/offers-terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>THIS USER GENERATED AGREEMENT (&amp;ldquo;Agreement&amp;rdquo;) affects your legal rights and requires you, the visitor, to enter into a legal and binding agreement with the CREDIT INFORMATION BUREAU (INDIA) LIMITED on behalf of itself and its affiliated entities (&amp;ldquo;CIBIL&amp;rdquo;). Please read this agreement very carefully and make sure you understand your rights and obligations before entering into this agreement and providing any consent to CIBIL. By tick marking the &amp;lsquo;I accept the Terms and Conditions&amp;rsquo; and clicking on the &amp;ldquo;Get Loan Offers&amp;rdquo; box on this website, you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions contained in this Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/legal-information/terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 14:32:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/legal-information/terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>This document lays out the terms and conditions and rules, as may be amended and supplemented, from time to time, (Terms) which shall be applicable to the provision of: (i) Credit Information Reports (Individual CIRs) and Company Credit Information Report (Company CIRs) (collectively referred to as, Reports) either /or for (a) Free Annual Credit Report and Score (as mandated by the Reserve Bank of India) (b) Subscribed Product ( Unlimited Access within the subscription period) (c) Featured Offers (d) Personalized Loan Offers to either an individual, a partnership firm, a company (as defined in section 2 (20) of the Companies Act, 2013 ), a body corporate (as defined under Section 2(11) of the Companies Act, 2013), a co-operative society, a trust, an association of persons whether incorporated or not, and any other entity, and shall include their heirs, representatives, successors and assigns, as permitted and applicable, (Persons) who can apply for the CIRs and/or the Commercial CIRs, under applicable law; (ii) Featured Offers and (iii) any other products and services rendered by TransUnion CIBIL to the Persons (collectively referred to as, Products and Services) by TransUnion TransUnion CIBIL Limited (&amp;ldquo;TransUnion CIBIL&amp;rdquo;) having its registered office at One World Center, 19th Floor, Tower 2A, Senapati Bapat Marg, Elphinstone Road, Mumbai - 400 013 (Transaction).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy policy</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/legal-information/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 13:40:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/legal-information/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>The contents of this privacy policy (&amp;ldquo;Privacy Policy&amp;rdquo;) along with the general terms and conditions (&amp;ldquo;General TNC&amp;rdquo;) available at http://www.transunioncibil.com/terms-and-conditions are applicable to all hyperlinks under http://www.transunioncibil.com (this &amp;ldquo;Website&amp;rdquo;) and http://www.cibil.com. You hereby acknowledge of having read and accepted the same by use or access of this Website. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we will notify the by means of a notice on our home page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/legal-information/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 13:19:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/legal-information/security/</guid>
      <description>TransUnion Interactive, Inc. understands the confidentiality of information contained in credit reports, and we safeguard the privacy of all information you provide to us through any TransUnion Interactive website.
Identity Verification System (IV)
TransUnion Interactive has designed an Identity Verification System in order to protect your security and privacy. IV seeks to confirm that your personal credit information is being viewed by YOU.
When a customer requests a credit report, IV is intended to confirm the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Cibil Score and How to Improve It</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/what-is-cibil-score-and-how-to-improve-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:15:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/what-is-cibil-score-and-how-to-improve-it/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
What is CIBIL Score and what factors affect my CIBIL Score?How can I improve my CIBIL Score?What is CIBIL Score and what factors affect my CIBIL Score?
CIBIL Score is a 3 digit numeric summary of your credit history, derived by using details found in the &amp;lsquo;Accounts&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Enquiries&amp;rsquo; sections on your CIBIL Report and ranges from 300 to 900. The closer your score is to 900, the higher are the chances of your loan application getting approved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A first time users guide to establishing credit</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/a-first-time-users-guide-to-establishing-credit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/a-first-time-users-guide-to-establishing-credit/</guid>
      <description>Simple steps can lead to a bright financial future
As a new entrant into the world of your own money and credit, here’s a quick primer about the basics to establishing a good credit record. Firstly, what is credit? Put simply, credit is a loan. The kind of credit you can get will depend on your CIBIL score. The higher it is, the more creditworthy you are from a lender’s perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alerts</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/dashboard-faqs/alerts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/dashboard-faqs/alerts/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
How can I get access to Alerts?What is the Alerts feature?
Your CIBIL Score and Report may change whenever a credit institution accesses your report or submits new and/or updated data on the credit facilities you have availed. The new Alerts feature monitors your CIBIL Score and Report and sends you real-time email notifications that your CIBIL Score and Report has undergone a change.
How does Alerts help me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All you need to know about CIBIL Score</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/all-you-need-to-know-about-cibil-score/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/all-you-need-to-know-about-cibil-score/</guid>
      <description>Are you aware of the CIBIL Score? Why is it important? Here’s an overview of what the CIBIL Score is, how it is calculated and why it is a key factor in our loan applications.
Your CIBIL score is an important factor that lenders look at while evaluating a loan application. Hence it’s important to understand how the score is calculated. While there is a proprietary algorithm that determines your CIBIL score, the most important elements of the score composition are based on an individual’s loan payment behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a positive credit profile with good credit habits</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/build-a-positive-credit-profile-with-good-credit-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/build-a-positive-credit-profile-with-good-credit-habits/</guid>
      <description>Good financial habits can help you create a positive credit profile. Here are a few key credit habits you should keep in mind when building and maintaining a positive credit profile.
If manners maketh a man, good habits are not far behind. All of us are creatures of habit — following our daily routines and schedules with admirable precision. And it is these very habits that have the potential to shape us into the best version of ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIBIL Alerts: Stay connected with your credit profile, always</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/cibil-alerts-stay-connected-with-your-credit-profile-always/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/cibil-alerts-stay-connected-with-your-credit-profile-always/</guid>
      <description>Stay updated and aware of key changes in your credit profile with CIBIL Alerts.
We have become increasingly dependent on alerts, which deliver time-sensitive information at our fingertips and help us stay connected with the world at large. Such alerts include weather forecasts, traffic updates, bank notifications, and any other time-sensitive information we might need to manage our physical and financial health.
When you are balancing the needs of your financial health with the desire to pursue your dreams, it is important to recognize the role credit plays in making those dreams a reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIBIL Dashboard &amp; Its Features</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/watch-and-listen/cibil-dashboard--its-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/watch-and-listen/cibil-dashboard--its-features/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIBIL Subscription Plans</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/dashboard-faqs/cibil-subscription-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/dashboard-faqs/cibil-subscription-plans/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
How do I purchase a CIBIL Subscription plan?What are CIBIL Subscription Plans?
These are time-based subscription plans for your CIBIL Score &amp;amp; Report. You can refresh your CIBIL Score &amp;amp; Report daily during the subscription period and have an option to choose either a 1 month (₹ 550/-), 6 months (₹ 800/-) or 12 months (₹ 1200/-) plan.
Depending upon the Plan that you choose, you also get access to other CIBIL features like CIBIL Alerts, Score Simulator, Personalized Loan Offers, Credit Monitoring and Dispute Assistance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt Trap: What to look out for if you have a credit card?</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/debt-trap-what-to-look-out-for-if-you-have-a-credit-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/debt-trap-what-to-look-out-for-if-you-have-a-credit-card/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
How can you avoid getting into a debt trap?The easiest way to make your loan search (and application) simpler and faster is to maintain a high CIBIL Score. Learn about the most common debt traps, and how to steer clear of it so that it does not affect your credit health negatively.
What are the signs that indicate that you are or may be getting in to a debt trap?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free CIBIL Score &amp; Report</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/free-cibil-score--report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/free-cibil-score--report/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
What additional features will I get access to along with my Free CIBIL Score and Report?What is a Free CIBIL Score and Report?
CIBIL provides you with one CIBIL Score and Report (without any charge) once in a calendar year. However, checking once is not enough and credit-conscious consumers should monitor their CIBIL Score and Report regularly to be loan-ready whenever the opportunity and need arises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get More with CIBIL Loan offers</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/watch-and-listen/get-more-with-cibil-loan-offers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/watch-and-listen/get-more-with-cibil-loan-offers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How CIBIL makes your loan search easier</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/dashboard-faqs/how-cibil-makes-your-loan-search-easier/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/dashboard-faqs/how-cibil-makes-your-loan-search-easier/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
See your Personalized Loan OffersTypically when we need a loan or a credit card, we approach at least 2-3 banks or financial institutions to find out interest rates and the other charges (such as processing charges). We then get all our documents in place and submit them to these lenders along with the loan application. Lenders now begin the &amp;lsquo;Loan evaluation&amp;rsquo; process by first referring your CIBIL Score and Report while assessing your application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to correct mistakes on your CIBIL report?</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/how-to-correct-mistakes-on-your-cibil-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/how-to-correct-mistakes-on-your-cibil-report/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
Inaccurate Current Balance or Amount OverdueIncorrect Personal DetailsOwnershipYour CIBIL Score and Report are important factors in the loan application process. Hence, inaccuracies on your credit report can result in reduced chances of a loan approval. It is very important for every credit-active individual to understand the types of inaccuracies that can occur and what it means for their CIBIL Report. CIBIL cannot alter any credit information in your report unless authorized by the Credit Institution (CI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to read and interpret your CIBIL report?</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/dashboard-faqs/how-to-read-and-interpret-your-cibil-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/dashboard-faqs/how-to-read-and-interpret-your-cibil-report/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
So, what exactly does your CIBIL report contain?We are all familiar with the fear and anxiety that we feel when applying for a loan. After all, it&amp;rsquo;s the lender who decides whether we can own our dream home, our first car, or whether our children can pursue higher education. In a nutshell, a better life depends on the lender&amp;rsquo;s decision.
We are unsure of the lender&amp;rsquo;s criteria to evaluate our application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loan Rejections and Disputes</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/loan-rejections-and-disputes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/loan-rejections-and-disputes/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
What kind of inaccuracies can reflect on my CIBIL report?My loan has been rejected because of the defaults reported against my name in CIBIL records. How do I remove my name from the CIBIL&amp;rsquo;s defaulters list?
CIBIL maintains the credit history of individuals as reported by lenders. The decision to grant a loan is solely dependent on the lender&amp;rsquo;s credit policy. Monitor your CIBIL Score and Report regularly and ensure you have a high score so that you are loan-ready when the need arises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myths and Facts</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/myths-and-facts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/myths-and-facts/</guid>
      <description>Myths and Facts
MYTH- CIBIL maintains list of defaulters only and having your name in CIBIL is bad.
FACT- If you have ever taken a loan or credit card from any bank or financial institution then your information is most likely with CIBIL. So your name will be with CIBIL even if you are paying all your obligations on time. RBI has mandated banks and financial institutions to submit monthly repayment data pertaining to those customers who have taken a loan or credit card with them to a Credit Bureau.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protect your identity with CIBIL Alerts</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/watch-and-listen/protect-your-identity-with-cibil-alerts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/watch-and-listen/protect-your-identity-with-cibil-alerts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Score Simulator</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/dashboard-faqs/score-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/dashboard-faqs/score-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
How does Score Simulator help me?What is Score Simulator?
Score Simulator is a tool that allows you to simulate different credit actions on your existing CIBIL Report, and generates a simulated CIBIL Score. This helps you understand how various credit actions can impact your existing CIBIL Score thus empowering you to take informed decisions.
How does the Score Simulator work?
The Score Simulator allows you to choose from various simulations - such as</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some of the common credit mistakes to avoid</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/some-of-the-common-credit-mistakes-to-avoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/some-of-the-common-credit-mistakes-to-avoid/</guid>
      <description>Let’s dive in now into the ways by which you can get off to a good start on your credit profile.
Your CIBIL score is a crucial indicator of your financial health, so good credit habits are essential to build and maintain a healthy profile. Let’s look at some of the common mistakes that can come in the way of fast and easy credit access.
Not Paying Bills on Time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Informed Credit Decisions Just Got Easier With the Score Simulator</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/taking-informed-credit-decisions-just-got-easier-with-the-score-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/latest-blogs/taking-informed-credit-decisions-just-got-easier-with-the-score-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered how your credit actions today can impact your access to future loans and credit? Read on to know how the Score Simulator helps you take an informed credit decision.
Imagine an alternate universe where you know how every single one of your actions may impact your future. Not only would this give you tremendous leverage over your peers, but would also make you wary of your decisions and actions, compelling you to deliberate and reconsider before behaving in a certain way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do while preparing for a loan application.</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/things-to-do-while-preparing-for-a-loan-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/credit-basics/things-to-do-while-preparing-for-a-loan-application/</guid>
      <description>Jump to:
Your CIBIL ScoreYour Credit EligibilityApplying for a loan can be a very unnerving and anxious process. You fill in lengthy forms, collect and submit various documents to multiple banks and then find yourself waiting with bated breath for loan approval while your plans for that dream home, your first car or your child&amp;rsquo;s education are kept waiting.
Your CIBIL Score
The first thing you should do is get your CIBIL Score and Report from Transunion CIBIL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understand Score Simulator</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/watch-and-listen/understand-score-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 02:10:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/credit-education/watch-and-listen/understand-score-simulator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is CIBIL Score and how to improve it?</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/sample-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 15:07:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/sample-article/</guid>
      <description>What is CIBIL Score and what factors affect my CIBIL Score?
CIBIL Score is a 3 digit numeric summary of your credit history, derived by using details found in the &amp;lsquo;Accounts&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Enquiries&amp;rsquo; sections on your CIBIL Report and ranges from 300 to 900. The closer your score is to 900, the higher are the chances of your loan application getting approved.
How can I improve my CIBIL Score?
You can improve your CIBIL Score by maintaining a good credit history, which is essential for loan approvals by lenders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Repayment Options</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/repayment-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 10:26:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/repayment-options/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Account</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/account/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:43:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/account/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loan Offers</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/loan-offers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:31:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/loan-offers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detailed Analysis</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/detailed-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 14:47:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/detailed-analysis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIBIL Report</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/cibil-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:12:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/cibil-report/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Score Simulator</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/score-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 17:48:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/score-simulator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade Plan</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/upgrade-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 14:49:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/upgrade-plan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alerts</title>
      <link>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/alerts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 14:47:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ajency.github.io/cibil-dashboard-paid/overview_paid/alerts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
